Narrator: Insects
Speaker 1: bee
Narrator: 2
Speaker 2: butterfly
Narrator: 6
Speaker 1: fly
Narrator: 3
Speaker 2: mosquito
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: spider
Narrator: 1
Speaker 2: wasp
Narrator: Farm animals
Speaker 1: bull
Narrator: 10
Speaker 2: chicken
Narrator: 12
Speaker 1: cow
Narrator: 7
Speaker 2: goat
Narrator: 13
Speaker 1: horse
Narrator: 11
Speaker 2: pig
Narrator: 9
Speaker 1: sheep
Narrator: Wild animals
Speaker 2: bat
Narrator: 18
Speaker 1: bear
Narrator: 21
Speaker 2: bird
Narrator: 14
Speaker 1: camel
Narrator: 26
Speaker 2: crocodile
Narrator: 28
Speaker 1: deer
Narrator: 17
Speaker 2: elephant
Narrator: 15
Speaker 1: giraffe
Narrator: 22
Speaker 2: kangaroo
Narrator: 20
Speaker 1: lion
Narrator: 19
Speaker 2: monkey
Narrator: 23
Speaker 1: mouse
Narrator: 25
Speaker 2: rabbit
Narrator: 27
Speaker 1: rat
Narrator: 29
Speaker 2: snake
Narrator: 24
Speaker 1: tiger
Narrator: Sea animals
Speaker 2: dolphin
Narrator: 30
Speaker 1: jellyfish
Narrator: 33
Speaker 2: shark
Narrator: 31
Speaker 1: whale